Guide to the Knight Kiplinger American statesmen portraiture collection, 1804-2001 MS2375
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Accession files, 1991-2001; Series 4; 2.5 Linear Feet
  - PR.PO.M.1587.U, 1991; Series 4 (Box 13, Folder 27)
  - PR.PO.M.1589.U, 1991; Series 4 (Box 13, Folder 28)
  - BS.EL.S.2495.F, 1992; Series 4 (Box 13, Folder 29)
  - MO.PO.S.2502 A.F, 1992; Series 4 (Box 13, Folder 30)
  - PH.EL.M.2513 B.F., 1995; Series 4 (Box 13, Folder 31)
  - MR.PO.L.2549.U, Undated; Series 4 (Box 13, Folder 32)
  - PR.PO.M.2800.U, Undated; Series 4 (Box 13, Folder 33)
  - PR.PO.M.2801.U, 1991; Series 4 (Box 13, Folder 34)
  - PR.PO.M.2802.U, 1991; Series 4 (Box 13, Folder 35)
  - PR.PO.M.2804.U, 1991; Series 4 (Box 13, Folder 36)
  - PR.PO.M.2805.U, Undated; Series 4 (Box 13, Folder 37)
  - PR.PO.M.2806.U, 1991; Series 4 (Box 13, Folder 38)
  - PR.PO.L.2803.U, 1997; Series 4 (Box 13, Folder 39)
  - PR.PO.L.2831.U, Undated; Series 4 (Box 13, Folder 40)
  - PR.PO.L.2851.U, Undated; Series 4 (Box 13, Folder 41)
  - PR.PO.L.2853.U, Undated; Series 4 (Box 13, Folder 42)
  - PH.PO.M.2854.U, Undated; Series 4 (Box 13, Folder 43)
  - PH.PO.M.2859.U, Undated; Series 4 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - PH.PO.M.2860.U, Undated; Series 4 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - PH.PO.L.2905.U, Undated; Series 4 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - MR.PO.S.2909.U, 1993; Series 4 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - PR.PO.L.2913.U, 1991; Series 4 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - PR.PO.L.2917.U, 1991; Series 4 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - PR.PO.L.2921.U, 1991; Series 4 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - PR.PO.L.2922.U, 1991; Series 4 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - PR.PO.L.2925.U, Undated; Series 4 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - PR.PO.L.2927.U, Undated; Series 4 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - PR.PO.L.2928.U, Undated; Series 4 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - PR.PO.L.2932.U, Undated; Series 4 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - PR.PO.L.2938.U, Undated; Series 4 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - PR.PO.M.2940.U, Undated; Series 4 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - PR.PO.L.2943.U, Undated; Series 4 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - PR.PO.L.2948.U, Undated; Series 4 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - PR.PO.L.2950.U, Undarted; Series 4 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - MR.PO.L.2954.U, Undated; Series 4 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - PR.PO.L.2959.U, Undated; Series 4 (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - PH.AC.L.2962.U, 1995; Series 4 (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - MR.PO.L.2975.U, Undated; Series 4 (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - MR.PO.L.2976.U, 1991; Series 4 (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - PH.AC.L.2977.F, 1993; Series 4 (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - MR.AC.L.2981.U, Undated; Series 4 (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - MR.PO.L.3111.U, Undated; Series 4 (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - PR.PO.L.3117.U, Undated; Series 4 (Box 14, Folder 26)
  - PH.PO.M.3128.U, Undated; Series 4 (Box 14, Folder 27)
  - PC.PO.S.3129.U, Undated; Series 4 (Box 14, Folder 28)
  - PR.PO.M.3138.U, 1991; Series 4 (Box 14, Folder 29)
  - PR.PO.M.3139.U, 1991; Series 4 (Box 14, Folder 30)
  - PR.PO.M.3140.U, 1997; Series 4 (Box 14, Folder 31)
  - PR.PO.M.3203.U, 1993; Series 4 (Box 14, Folder 32)
  - PH.PO.L.3214.U, Undated; Series 4 (Box 14, Folder 33)
  - PR.PO.L.3219.U, Undated; Series 4 (Box 14, Folder 34)
  - PR.PO.E.3225.U, Undated; Series 4 (Box 14, Folder 35)
  - MR.PO.L.3227.U, Undated; Series 4 (Box 14, Folder 36)
  - MR.PO.L.3229.U, Undated; Series 4 (Box 14, Folder 37)
  - MR.AC.L.3234.U, Undated; Series 4 (Box 14, Folder 38)
  - PH.PO.M.3238.U, Undated; Series 4 (Box 14, Folder 39)
  - PH.PO.M.3239.U, Undated; Series 4 (Box 14, Folder 40)
  - PR.PO.L.3244.U, Undated; Series 4 (Box 14, Folder 41)
  - PR.PO.L.3245.U, Undated; Series 4 (Box 14, Folder 42)
  - PR.PO.L.3246.U, Undated; Series 4 (Box 14, Folder 43)
  - PR.PO.L.3250.U, Undated; Series 4 (Box 14, Folder 44)
  - PR.PO.L.3251.U, Undated; Series 4 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - PR.PO.L.3252.U, Undated; Series 4 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - PR.PO.L.3253.U, Undated; Series 4 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - PR.PO.L.3254.U, Undated; Series 4 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - PR.PO.L.3255.U, Undated; Series 4 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - PR.PO.L.3256.U, Undated; Series 4 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - PH.PO.L.3257.U, Undated; Series 4 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - MR.PO.L.3262.U, Undated; Series 4 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - MR.PO.L.3263.U, Undated; Series 4 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - MR.PO.L.3264.U, Undated; Series 4 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - PR.PO.L3265.U, Undated; Series 4 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - MR.PO.L.3266.U, Undarted; Series 4 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - PR.PO.M.3291.U, Undated; Series 4 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - PH.PO.L.4181.U, Undated; Series 4 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - PR.PO.M.4189.U, Undated; Series 4 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - PR.AG.L.4217.F, 1996; Series 4 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - PH.PO.M.4323.F, 1991; Series 4 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - PR.PO.S.4477.U, Undated; Series 4 (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - PR.PO.L.4494.U, 1992; Series 4 (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - PR.PO.M.4536.U, 1992; Series 4 (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - PH.AG.E.4542.U, 1993; Series 4 (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - BS.PO.L.4548.U, 1993; Series 4 (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - MR.PO.M.4549.U, 1993; Series 4 (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - PR.PO.L.4552.U, 1993; Series 4 (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - BS.PO.E.4558.U, 1993; Series 4 (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - PR.PO.E.4559.U, 1993; Series 4 (Box 15, Folder 26)
  - MR.PO.E.4564.U, 1993; Series 4 (Box 15, Folder 27)
  - PR.CA.L.4573.U, 1993; Series 4 (Box 15, Folder 28)
  - PR.PO.L.4574.U, 1993; Series 4 (Box 15, Folder 29)
  - PR.PO.L.4575.U, 1993; Series 4 (Box 15, Folder 30)
  - PR.PO.E.4576.U, 1993; Series 4 (Box 15, Folder 31)
  - PR.PO.M.4577.U, 1993; Series 4 (Box 15, Folder 32)
  - 5085.PH.PO.M.F, 1996; Series 4 (Box 15, Folder 33)
  - 5087.PH.PO.M.F, 1996; Series 4 (Box 15, Folder 34)
  - 5088.PH.PO.L.F, Undated; Series 4 (Box 15, Folder 35)
  - 5103.PT.PO.L.F, 2001; Series 4 (Box 15, Folder 36)
  - PR.PO.L.3251.U, Undated; Series 4 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - PR.PO.L.3252.U, Undated; Series 4 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - PR.PO.L.3253.U, Undated; Series 4 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - PR.PO.L.3254.U, Undated; Series 4 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - PR.PO.L.3255.U, Undated; Series 4 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - PR.PO.L.3256.U, Undated; Series 4 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - PH.PO.L.3257.U, Undated; Series 4 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - MR.PO.L.3262.U, Undated; Series 4 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - MR.PO.L.3263.U, Undated; Series 4 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - MR.PO.L.3264.U, Undated; Series 4 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - PR.PO.L3265.U, Undated; Series 4 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - MR.PO.L.3266.U, Undarted; Series 4 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - PR.PO.M.3291.U, Undated; Series 4 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - PH.PO.L.4181.U, Undated; Series 4 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - PR.PO.M.4189.U, Undated; Series 4 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - PR.AG.L.4217.F, 1996; Series 4 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - PH.PO.M.4323.F, 1991; Series 4 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - PR.PO.S.4477.U, Undated; Series 4 (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - PR.PO.L.4494.U, 1992; Series 4 (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - PR.PO.M.4536.U, 1992; Series 4 (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - PH.AG.E.4542.U, 1993; Series 4 (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - BS.PO.L.4548.U, 1993; Series 4 (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - MR.PO.M.4549.U, 1993; Series 4 (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - PR.PO.L.4552.U, 1993; Series 4 (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - BS.PO.E.4558.U, 1993; Series 4 (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - PR.PO.E.4559.U, 1993; Series 4 (Box 15, Folder 26)
  - MR.PO.E.4564.U, 1993; Series 4 (Box 15, Folder 27)
  - PR.CA.L.4573.U, 1993; Series 4 (Box 15, Folder 28)
  - PR.PO.L.4574.U, 1993; Series 4 (Box 15, Folder 29)
  - PR.PO.L.4575.U, 1993; Series 4 (Box 15, Folder 30)
  - PR.PO.E.4576.U, 1993; Series 4 (Box 15, Folder 31)
  - PR.PO.M.4577.U, 1993; Series 4 (Box 15, Folder 32)
  - 5085.PH.PO.M.F, 1996; Series 4 (Box 15, Folder 33)
  - 5087.PH.PO.M.F, 1996; Series 4 (Box 15, Folder 34)
  - 5088.PH.PO.L.F, Undated; Series 4 (Box 15, Folder 35)
  - 5103.PT.PO.L.F, 2001; Series 4 (Box 15, Folder 36)
- Unsorted images, Series 5
  This series contains materials that have been identified as deserving of long-term retention, but have not yet been individually identified. The subjects include the same topics as in all the other series.
  - Unsorted Images - Oversized, Series 5 (Drawer 77)
  - Unsorted Images - Small-Medium, Series 5 (Box 9)
  - Unsorted Images - Large, Series 5 (Box 10)